A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - World Young Women's Christian Association - Tax Information, 1949, 1979 (Box 1104, Folder 6754)
    - Worldwatch Institute, 1973-1976 (Box 1104, Folder 6755-6758)
    - Worldwatch Institute, 1976 June-December (Box 1105, Folder 6759)
    - Yale University - Economic Growth Center, 1974-1978 (Box 1105, Folder 6760-6761)
    - Yale University - Economic Growth Center - Tax Information, 1975 (Box 1105, Folder 6762)
    - Yale University School of Medicine, 1959-1968 (Box 1105, Folder 6763)
    - Yankelovich, Skelly and White, Inc., 1983 (Box 1105, Folder 6764)
    - Young Filmmakers Foundation, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 1105, Folder 6765)
    - Young Filmmakers Foundation, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 1106, Folder 6766-6767)
    - Young Filmmakers Foundation, Inc. - Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 1106, Folder 6768)
    - Young Life Campaign, 1968-1974 (Box 1106, Folder 6769-6770)
    - Young Life Campaign - Tax Information, 1970-1981 (Box 1106, Folder 6771)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board, 1941-1954 (Box 1106, Folder 6772-6773)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board, 1955-1968 (Box 1107, Folder 6774-6779)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board, 1968-1971 (Box 1108, Folder 6780-6785)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board, 1971-1980 (Box 1109, Folder 6786-6790)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board - Tax Information, 1970-1974 (Box 1109, Folder 6791)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board - Building for Brotherhood Campaign, 1957-1960 (Box 1109, Folder 6792)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Greater New York, 1941-1951 (Box 1109, Folder 6793)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Greater New York, 1951-1976 (Box 1110, Folder 6794-6800)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Greater New York, 1977-1980 (Box 1111, Folder 6801)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Mount Vernon, 1976-1977 (Box 1111, Folder 6802)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Mount Vernon - Tax Information, 1971-1976 (Box 1111, Folder 6803)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Tarrytown, New York, 1941-1942 (Box 1111, Folder 6804)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown, 1971-1973 (Box 1111, Folder 6805)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown: Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 1111, Folder 6806)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - World Youth Fund, 1947 (Box 1111, Folder 6807)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1952-1964 (Box 1111, Folder 6808-6811)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1964-1973 (Box 1112, Folder 6812-6817)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1973-1982 (Box 1113, Folder 6818-6819)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Tax Information, 1970-1978 (Box 1113, Folder 6820)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of Brooklyn, 1963-1964 (Box 1113, Folder 6821)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of the City of New York, 1941-1953 (Box 1113, Folder 6822-6824)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of the City of New York, 1953-1970 (Box 1114, Folder 6825-6830)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of the City of New York, 1970-1983 (Box 1115, Folder 6831-6835)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of the City of New York - Tax Information, 1970-1980 (Box 1115, Folder 6836)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of the City of New York - YWCA and YMCA Joint Planning Project, 1970-1974 (Box 1116, Folder 6837-6840)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Mount Desert Island, 1972-1977 (Box 1116, Folder 6841-6842)
    - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Mount Desert Island - Tax Information, 1972-1975 (Box 1116, Folder 6843)
    - Young Women's Christian Association - Round the World Reconstruction Fund, 1947-1949 (Box 1117, Folder 6844)
    - Young Women's Christian Association - White Plains and Central Westchester, 1972-1974 (Box 1117, Folder 6845)
    - Young Women's Christian Association - White Plains and Central Westchester - Tax Information, 1972 (Box 1117, Folder 6846)
    - Youth Citizenship Fund, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 1117, Folder 6847-6851)
    - Youth Citizenship Fund, Inc. - Tax Information, 1971 (Box 1117, Folder 6852)
    - Youth Consultation Service of the Diocese of New York, 1945-1960 (Box 1118, Folder 6853)
    - Youth Consultation Service of the Diocese of New York, 1974-1977 (Box 1118, Folder 6854)
    - Youth for Understanding, 1970-1977 (Box 1118, Folder 6855-6858)
    - Youth for Understanding, 1977-1984 (Box 1119, Folder 6859-6864)
    - Youth for Understanding, 1984-1989 (Box 1120, Folder 6865-6867)
    - Youth for Understanding - Tax Information, 1973-1986 (Box 1120, Folder 6868)
    - Youthwork, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 1120, Folder 6869-6871)
    - Youth for Understanding, 1980-1982 (Box 1121, Folder 6872-6874)
    - Youth for Understanding - Tax Information, 1978-1980 (Box 1121, Folder 6875)
    - Zen Center, Rochester, Colorado, 1979 July-October (Box 1122, Folder 6883)
    - Zen Center, Rochester, Colorado, 1979-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 6884-6885)
    - Zen Center, A Corporation Sole, 1975-1976 (Box 1121, Folder 6876-6878)
    - Zen Center, A Corporation Sole, 1977-1983 (Box 1122, Folder 6879-6882)
    - Zen Studies Society, 1975-1982 (Box 1123, Folder 6886-6887)
    - Zen Studies Society - Tax Information, 1976-1980 (Box 1123, Folder 6888)
  - Projects (Grants), 1967-1996; 2
    - Accion International, 1984-1990 (Box 1124, Folder 6889-6891)
    - Accion International - Tax Information, 1970-1985 (Box 1124, Folder 6892)
    - Africa News Service, Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 1124, Folder 6893-6895)
    - Africa News Service, Inc. - Tax Information, 1979-1989 (Box 1125, Folder 6896)
    - AFS International-Intercultural Programs, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 1125, Folder 6897-6900)
    - AFS International-Intercultural Programs, Inc. - Tax Information, 1970-1986 (Box 1125, Folder 6901)
    - AFS International-Intercultural Programs, Inc. - Tax Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1126, Folder 6902)
    - Alaska Humanities Forum, 1984-1986 (Box 1126, Folder 6903)
    - Alaska Humanities Forum - Tax Information, 1985 (Box 1126, Folder 6904)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1980-1982 (Box 1126, Folder 6905-6907)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1982-1985 (Box 1127, Folder 6908-6913)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Daedalus, 1982-1991 (Box 1128, Folder 6914)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Magazines on the European Security Study Project, 1979-1982 (Box 1128, Folder 6915-6916)
    - American Association for the Magazines etc. on the European Security Study Project, 1982-1983 (Box 1128, Folder 6917)
    - American Association for the International Commission of Jurists, 1980-1982 (Box 1128, Folder 6918-6919)
    - American Association for the International Commission of Jurists, 1982-1986 (Box 1129, Folder 6920-6923)
    - American Association for the International Commission of Jurists - Tax Information, 1969-1986 (Box 1129, Folder 6924)
    - American Association of University Women Education Foundation, 1979-1984 (Box 1129, Folder 6925)
    - American Center for International Leadership, 1987 March-July (Box 1129, Folder 6926)
    - American Center for International Leadership, 1987-1989 (Box 1130, Folder 6927-6932)
    - American Center for International Leadership, 1989 April-August (Box 1131, Folder 6933-6935)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 1131, Folder 6936-6937)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) Foundation - Tax Information, 1970-1982 (Box 1131, Folder 6938)
    - American Conservation Association, 1981 (Box 1131, Folder 6939)
    - American Conservation Association - Tax Information, 1970-1981 (Box 1131, Folder 6940)
    - American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc., 1967, 1977-1983 (Box 1131, Folder 6941)
    - American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc. - Tax Information, 1970-1979 (Box 1131, Folder 6942)
    - American Council for Nationalities Service, Inc., 1977-1983 (Box 1132, Folder 6943)
    - American Council for Nationalities Service, Inc. - Tax Information, 1966-1977 (Box 1132, Folder 6944)
    - American Council for Learned Societies, 1980-1985 (Box 1132, Folder 6945-6950)
    - American Council for Learned Societies, 1986-1989 (Box 1133, Folder 6951-6955)
    - American Crafts Council, 1980-1982 (Box 1133, Folder 6956-6957)
    - American Crafts Council - Tax Information, 1970-1982 (Box 1133, Folder 6958)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1985-1988 (Box 1134, Folder 6959)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research - Tax Information, 1970-1983 (Box 1134, Folder 6960)
    - American Farmland Trust, 1980-1981 June (Box 1134, Folder 6961-6965)
    - American Farmland Trust, 1981 June-1982 (Box 1135, Folder 6966-6972)
    - American Farmland Trust, 1983 (Box 1136, Folder 6973-6978)
    - American Farmland Trust, 1983-1985 (Box 1137, Folder 6979-6984)
    - American Farmland Trust, 1985-1988 (Box 1138, Folder 6985-6990)
    - American Farmland Trust - Michigan Farmland Preservation Project, 1985-1986 (Box 1138, Folder 6991)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1980-1988 (Box 1139, Folder 6992-6994)
    - American Friends Service Committee - Tax Information, 1956-1980 (Box 1139, Folder 6995)
    - American Indian Lawyer Training Project, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 1139, Folder 6996-6998)
    - American Indian Lawyer Training Project, Inc. - Tax Information, 1973-1985 (Box 1139, Folder 6999)
    - Museum of the American Indian (Hey Foundation), 1980-1985 (Box 1140, Folder 7000)
    - Museum of the American Indian (Hey Foundation) - Tax Information, 1972-1982 (Box 1140, Folder 7001)
    - American Institute of Buddhist Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 1140, Folder 7002)
    - American Institute of Buddhist Studies - Tax Information, 1974-1982 (Box 1140, Folder 7003)
    - The American Jewish Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1140, Folder 7004-7005)
    - The American Jewish Committee - Tax Information, 1974-1980 (Box 1140, Folder 7006)
    - American Land Resource Association, 1980-1981 (Box 1140, Folder 7007)
      Formerly: American Land Forum.
    - American Land Resource Association, 1981-1988 (Box 1141, Folder 7008-7010)
    - American Land Resource Association - Tax Information, 1978-1981 (Box 1141, Folder 7011)
    - American Public Radio, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 1141, Folder 7012-7013)
    - American Public Radio, Inc. - Tax Information, 1983-1985 (Box 1141, Folder 7014)
    - American Red Cross in Greater New York, 1982-1984 (Box 1141, Folder 7015)
    - American Red Cross in Greater New York - Tax Information, 1973-1978 (Box 1141, Folder 7016)
    - The America's Society of International Law, 1977-1985 (Box 1141, Folder 7017)
    - The America's Society of International Law - Tax Information, 1974-1977 (Box 1141, Folder 7018)
    - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1986 January-June (Box 1141, Folder 7019)
    - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1986 June-1988 June (Box 1142, Folder 7020-7025)
    - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1988 June-1989 September (Box 1143, Folder 7026-7031)
    - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1990 (Box 1144, Folder 7032-7033)
    - American University of Beirut, 1983-1989 (Box 1144, Folder 7034-7035)
    - American Women's Economic Development Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box 1144, Folder 7037)
    - American Women's Economic Development Corporation - Tax Information, 1984-1987 (Box 1144, Folder 7038)
    - American Society, Inc., 1986 February-September (Box 1144, Folder 7039)
    - American Society, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 1145, Folder 7040-7041)
    - American Society, Inc. - Tax Information, 1986-1988 (Box 1145, Folder 7042)
    - Amigo Del Museo del Barrio, Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 1145, Folder 7043-7045)
    - Amigo Del Museo del Barrio, Inc. - Tax Information, 1973-1982 (Box 1145, Folder 7046)
    - Antigua-Caribbean Training Institute, Ltd., 1982-1986 (Box 1145, Folder 7047)
    - Antigua-Caribbean Training Institute, Ltd. - Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 1145, Folder 7048)
    - Archaeological Conservancy, 1979-1985 (Box 1146, Folder 7049-7050)
    - Arkansas Institute for Social Justice, Inc., 1976-1987 (Box 1146, Folder 7052)
    - Artisans Cooperation, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 1146, Folder 7053-7055)
    - Artisans Cooperation, Inc. - Tax Information, 1978-1981 (Box 1146, Folder 7056)
    - Arts, Education and Americans, Inc., 1975-1981 (Box 1147, Folder 7057-7062)
    - Arts, Education and Americans, Inc., 1981 November-1984 (Box 1148, Folder 7063-7064)
    - Arts, Education and Americans, Inc. - Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 1148, Folder 7065)
    - Arts, International, 1982-1985 (Box 1148, Folder 7066-7070)
    - Arts, International, 1986-1987 (Box 1149, Folder 7071)
    - Arts, International - Tax Information, 1981-1986 (Box 1149, Folder 7072)
    - Ashoka, 1981-1987 (Box 1149, Folder 7073-7077)
    - Ashoka, 1987 September-December (Box 1150, Folder 7078)
    - Asia Foundation, 1984-1990 (Box 1150, Folder 7079-7083)
    - Asia Society, 1982-1984 July (Box 1151, Folder 7084-7089)
    - Asia Society, 1984 July-1985 December (Box 1152, Folder 7090-7095)
    - Asia Society, 1985 December-1987 September (Box 1153, Folder 7096-7101)
    - Asia Society, 1987 September-1989 May (Box 1154, Folder 7102-7108)
    - Asia Society, 1989 May-October (Box 1155, Folder 7109--7114)
    - Asia Society, 1989 October-December (Box 1156, Folder 7115)
    - Asia Society - China Briefing, 1980, 1984, 1988-1989 (Box 1156, Folder 7116-7117)
    - Asian Institute of Technology, 1986-1988 (Box 1156, Folder 7118-7120)
    - Asian Institute of Technology, 1988-1989 (Box 1157, Folder 7121)
    - Association of The Bar of The City of New York Fund, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 1157, Folder 7122-7127)
    - Association of The Bar of The City of New York Fund, Inc. - Tax Information, 1982-1984 (Box 1157, Folder 7128)
    - Association of Black Social Workers Child Adoption Counseling and Referral Services, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 1158, Folder 7129-7130)
    - Association of Black Social Workers Child Adoption Counseling and Referral Services, Inc. - Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 1158, Folder 7131)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1986-1988 (Box 1158, Folder 7132-7134)
    - The Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 1158, Folder 7135)
    - The Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 1158, Folder 7136)
    - Association of Nonpublic Elementary and Secondary Schools of Illinois, 1984-1986 (Box 1159, Folder 7137)
    - Association of Nonpublic Elementary and Secondary Schools of Illinois - Tax Information, 1984-1986 (Box 1159, Folder 7138)
    - Association for Religious Communities, 1980 (Box 1159, Folder 7139)
    - Association for Religious Communities - Tax Information, 1976-1979 (Box 1159, Folder 7140)
    - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 1159, Folder 7141)
    - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. - Tax Information, 1970-1981 (Box 1159, Folder 7142)
    - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada, 1988-1989 (Box 1159, Folder 7143-7144)
    - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Tax Information (Box 1159, Folder 7145)
    - Atlanta University Center Corporation, 1980-1983 (Box 1159, Folder 7146)
    - College of the Atlantic, 1980-1985 (Box 1159, Folder 7147)
    - College of the Atlantic - Tax Information, 1969-1972 (Box 1159, Folder 7148)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States, 1976-1980 (Box 1159, Folder 7149-7151)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States, 1980-1987 (Box 1160, Folder 7152-7153)
    - The Australian National University, 1976-1985 (Box 1160, Folder 7154-7158)
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1980-1989 (Box 1161, Folder 7159)
    - Bank Street College of Education - Tax Information, 1975-1976 (Box 1161, Folder 7160)
    - Bar Association of The City of New York, 1984 (Box 1161, Folder 7161)
    - Barney and Associates, Inc., Gerald O., 1981-1984 (Box 1161, Folder 7162-7165)
    - Barney and Associates, Inc., Gerald O., 1984-1985 (Box 1162, Folder 7166-7167)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 1162, Folder 7168-7169)
    - Bay Area Institute, 1984-1988 (Box 1162, Folder 7170)
    - Bay Area Institute - Tax Information, 1979-1984 (Box 1162, Folder 7171)
    - Beijer Institute, 1978-1981, 1985 (Box 1162, Folder 7172)
    - Beijer Institute, 1985 July-December (Box 1163, Folder 7173-7177)
    - Beth Israel Medical Center, 1988 September (Box 1163, Folder 7178)
    - Beth Israel Medical Center, 1988-1993 (Box 1164, Folder 7179-7180)
    - Beth Israel Medical Center - Tax Information, 1982-1991 (Box 1164, Folder 7181)
    - Big Brothers Inc. of New York City, 1979-1981 (Box 1164, Folder 7182)
    - Big Brothers Inc. of New York City - Tax Information, 1970-1982 (Box 1164, Folder 7183)
    - Bio-Energy Council, 1983-1985 (Box 1164, Folder 7184-7185)
    - Bio-Energy Council, 1985-1987 (Box 1165, Folder 7186)
    - Bio-Energy Council - Tax Information, 1982-1987 (Box 1165, Folder 7187)
    - Biokultura Egyesulet (Bioculture Association), 1987-1991 (Box 1165, Folder 7188-7191)
    - Biokultura Egyesulet (Bioculture Association), 1991-1995 (Box 1166, Folder 7192)
    - Biokultura Egyesulet (Bioculture Association) - Tax Information, 1987-1990 (Box 1166, Folder 7193)
    - Biomass Users Network, 1984-1985 (Box 1166, Folder 7194-7197)
    - Biomass Users Network, 1985 September-1986 January (Box 1167, Folder 7198-7203)
    - Biomass Users Network, 1986-1988 (Box 1168, Folder 7204-7209)
    - Biomass Users Network, 1988-1990 (Box 1169, Folder 7210-7215)
    - Biomass Users Network, 1990-1993 (Box 1170, Folder 7216-7220)
    - Biomass Users Network - Tax Information, 1985-1992 (Box 1170, Folder 7221)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1991-1993 (Box 1171, Folder 7222-7226)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1993-1994 (Box 1172, Folder 7227-7229)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS - Tax Information, 1989-1994 (Box 1172, Folder 7230)
    - Bolivar Foundation, Inc., 1981 April-December (Box 1172, Folder 7231-7232)
    - Bolivar Foundation, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 1173, Folder 7233-7237)
    - Bolivar Foundation, Inc. - Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 1173, Folder 7238)
    - Boston Foundation, 1988 (Box 1174, Folder 7239-7242)
    - Botswana, Republic of, 1980-1983 (Box 1174, Folder 7243)
    - Botswana, Republic of - Tax Information, 1975-1978 (Box 1174, Folder 7244)
    - The Boys' Club Of New York, 1983-1985 (Box 1175, Folder 7245)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 1175, Folder 7246-7247)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc. - Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 1175, Folder 7248)
    - Broad Jump, Inc., 1985-1989 (Box 1175, Folder 7249-7250)
    - Broad Jump, Inc. - Tax Information, 1985-1987 (Box 1175, Folder 7251)
    - The Brookings Institution, 1983-1985 (Box 1175, Folder 7252-7253)
    - The Brookings Institution, 1985 June-July (Box 1176, Folder 7254-7256)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1981-1986 (Box 1176, Folder 7257-7259)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Tax Information, 1984-1986 (Box 1177, Folder 7260)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, 1982-1984 (Box 1177, Folder 7261)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation - Tax Information, 1977-1978 (Box 1177, Folder 7262)
    - Bryant Park Restoration Corporation, 1979-1987 (Box 1177, Folder 7263-7267)
    - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc., 1985-1993 (Box 1178, Folder 7268-7272)
    - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. - Tax Information, 1983-1988 (Box 1178, Folder 7273)
    - Cadec, Incorporated, Ltd., 1983-1984 (Box 1178, Folder 7273-7274)
    - Cadec, Incorporated, Ltd., 1984-1987 (Box 1179, Folder 7275-7276)
    - Cadec, Incorporated, Ltd. - Tax Information, 1977-1981 (Box 1179, Folder 7277)
    - CAF, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 1179, Folder 7278-7280)
    - CAF, Inc., 1982-1985 June (Box 1180, Folder 7281-7286)
    - CAF, Inc., 1985 July-1987 (Box 1181, Folder 7287-7292)
    - CAF, Inc., 1987 April-1988 October (Box 1182, Folder 7293-7298)
    - CAF, Inc., 1988 October-December (Box 1183, Folder 7299)
    - CAF, Inc. - Ad Hoc Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1183, Folder 7300)
    - CAF, Inc. - Agenda, 1973-1984 (Box 1183, Folder 7301-7305, Box 1184, Folder 7306-7311, Box 1185, Folder 7312-7318, Box 1186, Folder 7319-7320)
      Restricted - Confidential material - Permanently closed.
      Including Program Materials (Proposals and Summary Report)
    - CAF, Inc. - (Corporate) Executive Committee, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 1186, Folder 7321-7323)
      Restricted - Confidential Material - Permanently closed
    - CAF, Inc. - (Corporate) Minutes, 1969-1979 (Box 1186, Folder 7324)
    - CAF, Inc. - New Communities, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 1187, Folder 7325)
    - CAF, Inc. - Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 1187, Folder 7326)
    - CAF, Inc. - Program Investment, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 1187, Folder 7327)
    - CAF, Inc. - Trustees, 1969-1982 (Box 1187, Folder 7328-7331, Box 1188, Folder 7332-7334)
    - Regents of the University of California, Berkeley, 1977-1985 (Box 1188, Folder 7335-7337)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1980-1981 (Box 1189, Folder 7338-7343)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1981 April-1982 March (Box 1190, Folder 7344-7349)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1982 March-1983 November (Box 1191, Folder 7350-7355)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1983-1985 April (Box 1192, Folder 7356-7362)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1985 April-1986 November (Box 1193, Folder 7363-7368)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1986-1987 (Box 1194, Folder 7369-7371)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association - Marine Resources Program in the Eastern Caribbean, 1980-1982 (Box 1194, Folder 7372-7374)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association - Marine Resources Program in the Eastern Caribbean, 1982 June-1983 December (Box 1195, Folder 7375-7380)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association - Marine Resources Program in the Eastern Caribbean, 1984-1985 (Box 1196, Folder 7381-7382)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1980-1987 (Box 1196, Folder 7383-7387)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1987-1989 (Box 1197, Folder 7388-7393)
    - Center for Community Change, 1982-1984 (Box 1198, Folder 7395-7396)
    - Center for Community Economic Development, 1973-1978 (Box 1198, Folder 7397-7399)
    - Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange between East and West, 1976-1986 (Box 1198, Folder 7400)
    - Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange between East and West, 1986-1987 (Box 1199, Folder 7401)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1980-1985 (Box 1199, Folder 7402-7405)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations - Arts International, 1983-1984 (Box 1199, Folder 7406)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations - Tax Information, 1970-1984 (Box 1199, Folder 7407)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1983 (Box 1200, Folder 7408)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy - Tax Information, 1971-1983 (Box 1200, Folder 7409)
    - Center for Legislative Exchange, 1983 April-May (Box 1200, Folder 7409A)
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, 1983-1986 (Box 1200, Folder 7410, 7410A, 7410B)